{
    "question1": {
        "question": "What is the name for the Jewish New Year?",
        "answer1": "Hanukkah",
        "answer2": "Yom Kippur",
        "answer3": "Kwanza",
        "answer4": "Rosh Hashanah",
        "correct-answer": "Rosh Hashanah"
    },
    "question2": {
        "question": "How many blue stripes are there on the U.S. flag?",
        "answer1": "6",
        "answer2": "7",
        "answer3": "13",
        "answer4": "0",
        "correct-answer": "0"
    },
    "question3": {
        "question": "Which one of these characters is not friends with Harry Potter?",
        "answer1": "Ron Weasley",
        "answer2": "Neville Longbottom",
        "answer3": "Draco Malfoy",
        "answer4": "Hermione Granger",
        "correct-answer": "Draco Malfoy"
    },
    "question4": {
        "question": "What is the color of Donald Duck’s bowtie?",
        "answer1": "Red",
        "answer2": "Yellow",
        "answer3": "Blue",
        "answer4": "White",
        "correct-answer": "Red"
    },
    "question5": {
        "question": "What was the name of the band Lionel Richie was a part of?",
        "answer1": "King Harvest",
        "answer2": "Spectrums",
        "answer3": "Commodores",
        "answer4": "The Marshall Tucker Band",
        "correct-answer": "Commodores"
    },
    "question6": {
        "question": "Which animal does not appear in the Chinese zodiac?",
        "answer1": "Dragon",
        "answer2": "Rabbit",
        "answer3": "Dog",
        "answer4": "Hummingbird",
        "correct-answer": "Hummingbird"
    },
    "question7": {
        "question": "Which country held the 2016 Summer Olympics?",
        "answer1": "China",
        "answer2": "Ireland",
        "answer3": "Brazil",
        "answer4": "Italy",
        "correct-answer": "Brazil"
    },
    "question8": {
        "question": "Which planet is the hottest?",
        "answer1": "Venus",
        "answer2": "Saturn",
        "answer3": "Mercury",
        "answer4": "Mars",
        "correct-answer": "Venus"
    },
    "question9": {
        "question": "Who was the only U.S. President to resign?",
        "answer1": "Herbert Hoover",
        "answer2": "Richard Nixon",
        "answer3": "George W. Bush",
        "answer4": "Barack Obama",
        "correct-answer": "Richard Nixon"
    },
    "question10": {
        "question": "What does the “D” in “D-Day” stand for?",
        "answer1": "Dooms",
        "answer2": "Dark",
        "answer3": "Day",
        "answer4": "Dunkirk",
        "correct-answer": "Day"
    },
    "question11": {
        "question": "In which city can you find the Liberty Bell?",
        "answer1": "Washington, D.C.",
        "answer2": "Boston",
        "answer3": "Philadelphia",
        "answer4": "Manhattan",
        "correct-answer": "Philadelphia"
    },
    "question12": {
        "question": "In Pirates of the Caribbean, what was Captain Jack Sparrow’s ship’s name?",
        "answer1": "The Marauder",
        "answer2": "The Black Pearl",
        "answer3": "The Black Python",
        "answer4": "The Slytherin",
        "correct-answer": "The Black Pearl"
    },
    "question13": {
        "question": "According to Forrest Gump, 'life was like…'",
        "answer1": "A bag of lemons",
        "answer2": "A handful of roses",
        "answer3": "A lollipop",
        "answer4": "A box of chocolates",
        "correct-answer": "A box of chocolates"
    },
    "question14": {
        "question": "Linda and Bob from Bob’s Burgers have 3 kids. Which one of these characters is not one of them?",
        "answer1": "Louise",
        "answer2": "Gene",
        "answer3": "Jimmy",
        "answer4": "Tina",
        "correct-answer": "Jimmy"
    },
    "question15": {
        "question": "The British band One Direction, was made up of Harry, Louis, Niall, Zayn, and…",
        "answer1": "Paul",
        "answer2": "Callum",
        "answer3": "Kevin",
        "answer4": "Liam",
        "correct-answer": "Liam"
    },
    "question16": {
        "question": "What is the rarest blood type?",
        "answer1": "O",
        "answer2": "A",
        "answer3": "B",
        "answer4": "AB-Negative",
        "correct-answer": "AB-Negative"
    },
    "question17": {
        "question": "Holly Golightly is a character in which film?",
        "answer1": "Breakfast at Tiffanys",
        "answer2": "Pretty In Pink",
        "answer3": "Funny Face",
        "answer4": "Singing In The Rain",
        "correct-answer": "Breakfast at Tiffanys"
    },
    "question18": {
        "question": "In The Wizard of Oz, the Tin Man wanted to see the Wizard about getting…",
        "answer1": "A brain",
        "answer2": "An oil can",
        "answer3": "A dog",
        "answer4": "A heart",
        "correct-answer": "A heart"
    },
    "question19": {
        "question": "Which American state is known as the sunflower state?",
        "answer1": "Florida",
        "answer2": "California",
        "answer3": "Maine",
        "answer4": "Kansas",
        "correct-answer": "Kansas"
    },
    "question20": {
        "question": "Which one of these characters isn’t a part of the Friends group?",
        "answer1": "Rachel",
        "answer2": "Joey",
        "answer3": "Gunther",
        "answer4": "Monica",
        "correct-answer": "Gunther"
    },
    "question21": {
        "question": "How many bones are there in the human body?",
        "answer1": "206",
        "answer2": "205",
        "answer3": "201",
        "answer4": "209",
        "correct-answer": "206"
    },
    "question22": {
        "question": "Which famous singer released a song called “Adore You”?",
        "answer1": "Harry Styles",
        "answer2": "Dua Lipa",
        "answer3": "Halsey",
        "answer4": "Shawn Mendes",
        "correct-answer": "Harry Styles"
    },
    "question23": {
        "question": "Fe is the chemical symbol for…",
        "answer1": "Zinc",
        "answer2": "Hydrogen",
        "answer3": "Fluorine",
        "answer4": "Iron",
        "correct-answer": "Iron"
    },
    "question24": {
        "question": "How old do you have to be to enter the hunger games?",
        "answer1": "12",
        "answer2": "11",
        "answer3": "10",
        "answer4": "15",
        "correct-answer": "12"
    },
    "question25": {
        "question": "What language is the most spoken worldwide?",
        "answer1": "Chinese",
        "answer2": "Spanish",
        "answer3": "Arabic",
        "answer4": "English",
        "correct-answer": "English"
    },
    "question26": {
        "question": "What year did Barbie come out?",
        "answer1": "1958",
        "answer2": "1959",
        "answer3": "1956",
        "answer4": "1961",
        "correct-answer": "1959"
    },
    "question27": {
        "question": "What is Shakespeare’s shortest tragedy?",
        "answer1": "Macbeth",
        "answer2": "Hamlet",
        "answer3": "Romeo & Juliet",
        "answer4": "Othello",
        "correct-answer": "Macbeth"
    },
    "question28": {
        "question": "What is the #1 cookie in the U.S.?",
        "answer1": "Chips Ahoy!",
        "answer2": "Milano",
        "answer3": "Girl Scout",
        "answer4": "Oreo",
        "correct-answer": "Oreo"
    },
    "question29": {
        "question": "How many hearts does an octopus have?",
        "answer1": "1",
        "answer2": "2",
        "answer3": "3",
        "answer4": "4",
        "correct-answer": "3"
    },
    "question30": {
        "question": "Who wrote The Scarlett Letter?",
        "answer1": "Shakespeare",
        "answer2": "Stephen King",
        "answer3": "Nathanial Hawthorne",
        "answer4": "Ernest Hemingway",
        "correct-answer": "Nathanial Hawthorne"
    },
    "question31": {
        "question": "Which social media platform came out in 2003?",
        "answer1": "Myspace",
        "answer2": "Twitter",
        "answer3": "Facebook",
        "answer4": "Tumblr",
        "correct-answer": "Myspace"
    },
    "question32": {
        "question": "Which planet in our solar system is the largest?",
        "answer1": "Jupiter",
        "answer2": "Saturn",
        "answer3": "Neptune",
        "answer4": "Earth",
        "correct-answer": "Jupiter"
    },
    "question33": {
        "question": "The Powerpuff Girls are 3 distinct colors. What are they?",
        "answer1": "Red, yellow, green",
        "answer2": "Yellow, blue, green",
        "answer3": "Blue, green, red",
        "answer4": "Green, purple, orange",
        "correct-answer": "Blue, green, red"
    },
    "question34": {
        "question": "Which boyband sings the song 'I Want It That Way'?",
        "answer1": "One Direction",
        "answer2": "Backstreet Boys",
        "answer3": "NSYNC",
        "answer4": "New Kids On The Block",
        "correct-answer": "Backstreet Boys"
    },
    "question35": {
        "question": "Who painted the Sistine Chapel ceiling?",
        "answer1": "Picasso",
        "answer2": "Da Vinci",
        "answer3": "Michelangelo",
        "answer4": "Van Gogh",
        "correct-answer": "Michelangelo"
    },
    "question36": {
        "question": "In which state did the Salem Witch Trials take place?",
        "answer1": "Washington",
        "answer2": "Virginia",
        "answer3": "Massachusetts",
        "answer4": "Pennsylvania",
        "correct-answer": "Massachusetts"
    },
    "question37": {
        "question": "Which ocean is the largest?",
        "answer1": "Indian",
        "answer2": "Pacific",
        "answer3": "Atlantic",
        "answer4": "Arctic",
        "correct-answer": "Pacific"
    },
    "question38": {
        "question": "Which New York City building is the tallest:",
        "answer1": "Empire State Building",
        "answer2": "Bank of America Tower",
        "answer3": "One World Trade Center",
        "answer4": "Statue of Liberty",
        "correct-answer": "One World Trade Center"
    },
    "question39": {
        "question": "What does the “E” in Chuck E. Cheese stand for?",
        "answer1": "Ernest",
        "answer2": "Edward",
        "answer3": "Entertainment",
        "answer4": "Extra",
        "correct-answer": "Entertainment"
    },
    "question40": {
        "question": "Which country gifted the Statue of Liberty to the U.S.?",
        "answer1": "Germany",
        "answer2": "China",
        "answer3": "France",
        "answer4": "Italy",
        "correct-answer": "France"
    },
    "question41": {
        "question": "Who painted the Mona Lisa?",
        "answer1": "Van Gogh",
        "answer2": "da Vinci",
        "answer3": "Picasso",
        "answer4": "Monet",
        "correct-answer": "da Vinci"
    },
    "question42": {
        "question": "In which city were Anne Frank and her family in hiding?",
        "answer1": "Paris",
        "answer2": "Amsterdam",
        "answer3": "Brussels",
        "answer4": "Frankfurt",
        "correct-answer": "Amsterdam"
    },
    "question43": {
        "question": "There are 4 best friends on the TV show Pretty Little Liars: Hanna, Emily, Aria, and…",
        "answer1": "Mona",
        "answer2": "Charlie",
        "answer3": "Alison",
        "answer4": "Spencer",
        "correct-answer": "Spencer"
    },
    "question44": {
        "question": "In which decade does the Netflix series Stranger Things take place?",
        "answer1": "the ‘70s",
        "answer2": "the ‘80s",
        "answer3": "the ‘90s",
        "answer4": "the early 2000s",
        "correct-answer": "the ‘80s"
    },
    "question45": {
        "question": "Which country consumes the most chocolate?",
        "answer1": "Spain",
        "answer2": "Germany",
        "answer3": "North America",
        "answer4": "Switzerland",
        "correct-answer": "Switzerland"
    },
    "question46": {
        "question": "What is Sodium Chloride?",
        "answer1": "Salt",
        "answer2": "Sugar",
        "answer3": "Chlorine",
        "answer4": "Bleach",
        "correct-answer": "Salt"
    },
    "question47": {
        "question": "Which astrological sign is a crab?",
        "answer1": "Pisces",
        "answer2": "Aquarius",
        "answer3": "Cancer",
        "answer4": "Virgo",
        "correct-answer": "Cancer"
    },
    "question48": {
        "question": "In the Bible, how does the Virgin Mary learn of her pregnancy with baby Jesus?",
        "answer1": "God tells her",
        "answer2": "the angel Gabriel tells her",
        "answer3": "she has a dream about it",
        "answer4": "a doctor tells her",
        "correct-answer": "the angel Gabriel tells her"
    },
    "question49": {
        "question": "Who, in the Harry Potter series, is Tom Riddle?",
        "answer1": "a student in Harry’s class",
        "answer2": "a professor at Hogwarts",
        "answer3": "Harry’s birth father",
        "answer4": "Voldemort",
        "correct-answer": "Voldemort"
    },
    "question50": {
        "question": "The movie The Social Network is about which social media platform:",
        "answer1": "Facebook",
        "answer2": "Myspace",
        "answer3": "Instagram",
        "answer4": "Twitter",
        "correct-answer": "Facebook"
    }
}